(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-03T23:30:19.042174",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
お気に召すまま
[Song: As You Like It]
淡々と言葉を吐いた
I indifferently spat out words.
あんな思い出に泣いたのは
Crying over those memories...
今日で終わりにしないか
...shall we end it today?
1、2の合図を待って
Waiting for the signal of one, two,
ユー・アンド・ミー 手を取り合ったのは
you and me held hands...
僕の勇気ある行動
...due to my courageous action.
フェイズ
Phase.
立ち止まらないでいいんだからね
It's fine not to stop, you know.
空々しいな この人生
How empty this life is.
できないなんて言わないでね
Don't say you can't do it.
言わないでね
Don't say it.
今更なんて言わないでね
Don't tell me it's too late now.
僕ら今さあさあ輪になって
Now, let's gather in a circle...
回り始める
...and start spinning around.
段々嫌になって
Gradually growing to hate it,
でも好きになる
but then falling in love with it.
ねえねえわかんないや
Hey, I just don't get it,
自分会議も
even my inner meetings.
どんどん中に寄って
Drawing closer and closer,
でも離れてく
but then drifting apart.
ぱっぱっ音に乗って
Moving along with the rhythm...
踊り始める
...and starting to dance.
散々嫌になって
Utterly growing to hate it,
でも好きになる
but then falling in love with it.
ねえねえわかんないや
Hey, I just don't get it.
この先もずっと
From now on and forever,
僕の心をシェイクシェイク いえい
shake my heart, shake it, yeah!
大正解なんてないのさ
There is no single correct answer.
じゃあ一体どこに向かえば
So, where on earth should we head...
物語は終わりますか
...for the story to come to an end?
1、2の合図を待って
Waiting for the signal of one, two,
ユー・アンド・ミー 手が触れ合ったのは
you and me, our hands touching...
僕の勇気ある行動
...due to my courageous action.
フェイズ
Phase.
畏まったって意味ないんだって
There's no point in being so formal.
恥ずかしがった夢にバイバイです
Say goodbye to the embarrassed dream.
この先ずっとよろしくね よろしくね
Please look after me from now on, okay?
君と今さあさあ交わって
Now, let's mingle together...
目を逸らしあう
...and avert our eyes from each other.
段々嫌になって
Gradually growing to hate it,
でも好きになる
but then falling in love with it.
ねえねえわかんないや
Hey, I just don't get it,
自分会議も
even my inner meetings.
どんどん様になって
Becoming more and more fitting,
崩れ落ちてく
but then crumbling down.
ぱっぱっ触れる前に
Quickly, before we even touch,
消えてしまうの
it disappears.
散々嫌になって
Utterly growing to hate it,
でも好きになる
but then falling in love with it.
ねえねえわかんないや
Hey, I just don't get it.
この先もずっと
From now on and forever,
分かり合えるまで僕たちはダンスを
until we can understand each other, we'll keep dancing.
今更なんて言わないでね
Don't tell me it's too late now.
僕ら今さあさあ輪になって
Now, let's gather in a circle...
回り始める
...and start spinning around.
段々嫌になって
Gradually growing to hate it,
でも好きになる
but then falling in love with it.
ねえねえわかんないや
Hey, I just don't get it,
自分会議も
even my inner meetings.
どんどん中に寄って
Drawing closer and closer,
でも離れてく
but then drifting apart.
ぱっぱっ音に乗って
Moving along with the rhythm...
踊り始める
...and starting to dance.
散々嫌になって
Utterly growing to hate it,
でも好きになる
but then falling in love with it.
ねえねえわかんないや
Hey, I just don't get it.
この先もずっと
From now on and forever,
僕の心をシェイクシェイク いえい
shake my heart, shake it, yeah!
Wow!
Oh my god, did you see us? We're so cute!
All four of us are so cute together.
I loved that concert.
This is where the money is at.
Yeah, the money's in the concert.
It was so nice to see everyone perform.
More concerts, more music.
If only there was a concert that was coming up.
Ah, if only.
If only there were tickets available right now...
...for a concert.
Serendipity... I wonder where that word came from.
Serendipity.
Wait! What if we invite even more people?
But if we invite more people, won't be a concert anymore.
Because when there's more people, they start fighting.
You mean drama?
Drama.
Wait, that's gonna... You get too many girls in a room, drama happens.
But that sells.
I love seeing girls fight.
Sometimes there's just too many girls, you know.
Yeah.
And sometimes they just can't get along.
But, that makes for good television. We should film them.
Let's content farm them!
FOLLOWING UP ON THE HOLOLIVE-ENIANS
[Title: Following Up on the Hololive-ENians]
LOS ANGELES
[Location: Los Angeles]
GINA'S CONDO
[Location: Gina's Condo]
Oh my god girls, if you want to hang out with us,
you have to step up your bag game.
Like, where did you even get your bag from? It looks...
You don't even recognize the bag I carried today?
Oh, you... Next time we're gonna have to take you to, like, Benella.
Benella?
Yeah.
I own that company.
Oh, you own Benella?!
I own the sister brand of Benella.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, what are you cooking?
Oh, it's my newest recipe. It's a zero-calorie...
Oh shit!
It's a zero-calorie...
Oh my god!
Oh shit!
Oh my god, what the...
What happened?
Are you going to pick that up?
Don't tell me what to do!
You literally threw it on the ground.
No, I didn't.
You literally did it, you can't accidentally throw something on the ground.
No, I didn't, you put it there.
I put it there?
You put your ass in my stupid kitchen, you bitch!
You absolute cunt!
I did not do that!
You literally did, you always make shit up!
This always happens...
I watched you, did you see her do that?
Did you see that? She literally threw...
Oh yeah, I saw that, sis. I saw you throw a frying pan.
I saw you throw a frying pan, pastel.
No, I didn't!
Excuse me!
Yeah, so I was making this totally delicious zero-calorie option...
...dinner for everyone, because I know that everyone needs to lose a little weight for the party tomorrow.
And, I just can't believe that she would do such a thing.
Have you seen Celine? She's a total fucking bitch!
That food is going to be nasty, and you know it.
She's always on these, like, health trips, but it doesn't do anything for her figure.
Come... Come here.
Don't tell me what to do!
Come here! Come here! You're not my mom!
Look. Look at it. You threw that on the ground.
I've never seen that in my entire life.
How have you never seen that in your entire life?
I've never seen that in my entire life. Did you get this for me for Christmas?
I would never get you something for Christmas.
What? You got it for me for Christmas!
No, I don't know what you're talking...
You always do this! Someone hold me back! Hold me back! Hold me back!
Hey hey hey hey, leave her, leave my friend alone!
Are you okay? It's okay, it's okay, don't cry, you're gonna ruin your makeup, girl.
Oh my god, you're so dramatic, so dramatic.
How dare you! She is crazy!
She is crazy! Did you...
Shut the fuck up!
Who even are you?
I don't know why the fuck I'm here!
I was just here to, like, promote my music, and like,
all of these, you know, really rich girls here.
I'm so honored to be here, honestly, but...
...I don't know what the fuck went on.
Like, what the fuck?
I think it's the water.
There's something in the water.
I don't even know why Irene was here.
Who invited her?
She's sexy.
Why are you always so dramatic?
Me, dramatic?
Why do you always make shit up?
You are fake! You are fake!
The only thing about me that's fake...
...is my tits!
You talk to her like that, you...
Yeah, her tits are fake. I would know, I paid for them.
Well, I was really insecure about my chest, so, you know, I got it. Well, you know, Daddy paid for- No.
Wait, was it Gyana? Oh my god, I forgot about that.
I owe her. She's the best.
It's fine. Are you okay?
I'm not okay. I'm literally not okay. Did you see what she did to me?
I saw. That was unbelievable. Our food, I was looking forward to that.
And it was a low-calorie option!
Like, you should stop acting like that, you know. How old are you? Excuse me?
I don't want to talk to her. Get away from me.
Shut up!
Oh my god, Bijou always has my back, girl. I know she'll throw down with me.
Are you getting my good side? Make sure you get the right angle. This is for TV, right? Yeah, check me out.
Anyway, Celine is a bitch.
I don't know what kind of problem she has with my girl Gyana, but if she continues with this, we're gonna have to throw hands.
She better catch me outside, how about that, if you know what I mean. I think she needs a wake-up call.
Bijou is such a follower. She doesn't have a single thought in that empty head of hers. If you were to take her head and rattle it, it would sound like a baby rattle.
You guys are so loud, we're gonna get a noise complaint, and it's gonna be so embarrassing for you, because this is my apartment.
The only noise complaint we'll get is when you're in your bedroom!
What is that supposed to mean?! Bedroom?!
You know what? Well, at least this apartment isn't under my name, so you are gonna get in trouble.
I will send you to jail, my daddy's a lawyer!
Well, you know what? My daddy owns your daddy!
My daddy might be under your daddy, but...
...he's a lawyer!
I think your daddy is under my daddy in more ways than one.
Do you see what she's doing to me, Bijou?
I saw, girl.
Oh, so you have a problem with Joan and Iris?
Don't touch her ever again, you understand?!
Oh my god, who do you think you are?! Get off her!
She pushed me!
Rachel threw herself on the floor, I saw it happen. She's just so dramatic.
Wow, she's such a pick-me girl. That Rachel...
...what a pick-me. Kind of a bitch.
I'd pick her, though. Have you seen her thunder thighs?
Dang, I wanna bite that. Don't tell her, though! Cut that out! Cut that out!
Quella stronza... ma non ti azzardare con quella cagna...
That bitch... don't you dare with that cunt...
Se ci prova ancora, quella vacca...
If she tries that again, that cow...
Se mi tocca di nuovo, io non ce la faccio più, basta, ho finito.
If she touches me again, I can't take it anymore. That's it, I'm done.
Rachel is so sweet, she always has my back. Sometimes she falls down though, but, you know, it helps for my cause, so it's okay.
Sure, you have a problem, and you are a danger to society...
I'm a danger?!
Watch out, watch out! Stop, stop!
Stop touching each other! This is getting a little too far, I think.
I got you, girl. I got you. Get up, get up right now, you're ruining your outfit!
Anyways, guys, I'm kind of hungry. Do you want...
I want food. What are you making?
I was making a new low-calorie recipe because you really need to slim down.
I was trying to help you!
If you are cooking, I guess everyone's going to lose their appetite.
Yeah, don't feed me anymore.
I thought Gyana was trained by a Michelin chef.
I was!
No, she's just lying, she always makes up this shit.
Namaste, namaste, namaste...
Oh, I can expect something so nutritious.
It's really nutritious.
How dare you try to ruin our perfect five-star meal!
It was really delicious.
We made a really good choice.
You ruined Thanksgiving!
She can do whatever she wants, and you are no one to tell her...
Well, I can say whatever I want, sister.
I lied.
Leave Bijou alone, Rachel. Leave Bijou alone.
So, what are we here for anyways?
Dinner! Dinner! Dinner!
Do we get to actually eat?
Are we going to eat? That's right!
We are going to eat!
Anyways, I wanna go back to the kitchen and I'm gonna finish cooking.
Yeah, where you belong!
You little...
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Who's gonna hold me back? Back off of her!
Oh, you... abuse! Abuse!
Are you okay, girl? Girl, are you okay?
Animal abuse? Animal abuse?
Just 'cause your dad is a lawyer doesn't mean you can do whatever...
Ugh, the forks not suit you?
Make me look good in the edit, okay?
Check out my mouth.
I feel like that was too many swear words.
I think they said- there's too many beepings in there.
Yeah, it was almost like a Morse code.
Like, they didn't even censor 'fuck'!
Or 'shit'.
Ah, I just... I don't know...
I would never swear on your channel, by the way.
Yeah, you're so sweet. That's really nice of you.
I would never fucking do that. That's so messed up of someone to do.
Yeah, I just...
Really fucked up.
I just wish they would have edited that out, you know?
Yeah, I just... I'm really uncomfortable right now.
I'm only...
five minutes old, I'm not allowed to hear those words!
I'm just really scared, and also...
...I don't think we're gonna make any money out of that because it's not gonna be allowed to be aired.
They demonetized our channel!
What if... what if we have...
...a show, but instead of like real people, it's scripted?
Oh, yeah! And then we can make sure there's no curse words in it, we'll take them all out!
Yeah, yeah! Scripted.
It can still be drama, right?
Mmhmm. But just no... no...
no curse...
No cursing, please!
Please, no cursing on our channel.
FORTNITE AWAY FROM DEATH
PREVIOUSLY ON: HALF A FORTNITE AWAY FROM DEATH - THE TALE OF BEAVER AND THINKER
Two unlikely survivors find each other in the middle of the apocalypse,
and although wary, they've come to find comfort in each other's presence.
Haunted by their past, afraid of a future that may never come,
will they ever be able to overcome their struggles in a dying world?
So, have you thought about it?
You just feel, you just always say things, but in reality, you...
I love you.
No, you love your wife!
She's dead now.
You don't even remember!
Even if she's dead, that doesn't mean she's not there anymore!
And I've been thinking about it, because I'm the Thinker.
Ooh, what are you?
I'm the Beaver.
Oh man, if I was a beaver, I'd be eating so good right now!
Is that wood?
Yeah, cuz I have wood! Look at my wood! Check it out!
So you would leave for nothing.
I can provide for you.
But you love your wife! You don't understand!
But still, your wife!
The past seven days...
...that we've learned to survive.
You just want me for my body.
You're not interested in my mind.
I want you for your mind! I'm the Thinker! I want you!
No. No.
No, you have to understand!
You're wrong!
No, please!
Check out my wood!
No! I don't want to look at your wood!
Look at my wood!
Oh, please!
I don't want your wood! I don't...
But you'll be so full!
No! Ew, ew! Put that away!
Look at my wood!
You don't even want me for my mind.
A skeleton!
Run away, run away! I'll protect us!
Please! I mean...
Beaver!
I'm the Beaver! I'm not Gigi, I'm the Beaver!
Beaver, be careful!
Oh my god, where did you get that weapon? I've never seen you use that before.
Yeah, I bought it from that one pawnshop owner, remember?
Oh yeah, that guy!
Was it Suou?
Was it Suou-mi?
No.
Watch out, Cecilia! Watch out!
Watch out! Watch out!
Oh my god, that's so cool!
Oh my god, that's so cool! Woah!
What's that? A skeleton dance?
Oh, she's just...
It's too strong!
Oh, it's just so cool!
いつか君が
Someday, you...
瞳に灯す愛の光が
...will kindle the light of love in your eyes,
時を超えて
transcending time...
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
...and destroying a dream of this world
確かに一つ壊すだろう
that is hurrying toward its ruin.
躊躇いを飲み干して
Swallowing your hesitation,
君が望むものは何？
what is it that you wish for?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
On the path of such greedy yearning,
儚い明日はあるの？
is there a fleeting tomorrow?
子供の頃夢に見た
Like the ancient magic
古の魔法のように
I used to dream of as a child,
闇さえ砕く力で
with a power that can shatter even the darkness,
微笑む君に会いたい
I want to meet you smiling.
怯えるこの手の中には
What I hold in these frightened hands of mine
手折られた花の勇気
is the courage of a plucked flower.
想いだけが頼る全て
My feelings alone are all that I rely upon...
光を呼び覚ます
...to awaken the light.
願い
My wish.
いつか君も誰かの為に
Someday, you will also wish...
強い力を望むのだろう
...for great power for the sake of someone else.
愛が胸を捉えた夜に
In the night when love captures your heart,
未知の言葉が生まれて来る
unknown words will be born.
迷わずに進めるなら
If I can move forward without losing my way,
心が砕けてもいいわ
I don't mind if my heart is broken to pieces.
いつも目の前の哀しみに
To stand up against the sorrow...
立ち向かう為の呪文が欲しい
...always right in front of my eyes, I want a spell.
君はまだ夢見る記憶
You are a memory that still dreams.
私は眠らない明日
I am the sleepless tomorrow.
二人が出会う奇跡を
To win the miracle...
勝ち取る為に進むわ
...of our meeting, I will move forward.
怯えるこの手の中には
What I hold in these frightened hands of mine
手折られた花の刃
is the blade of a plucked flower.
想いだけが生きる全て
My feelings alone are all that I live for...
心に振りかざす
...brandishing my wish...
願い
...in my heart.
囚われた太陽の輝く
When I used to like books...
不思議の国の本が好きだった頃
...about strange lands where the captive sun shines,
願いはきっと叶うと
I believed the fairy tales...
教えるお伽噺を信じた
...that taught us wishes would surely come true.
静かに咲き乱れていた
Gently, the ancient magic...
古の魔法優しく
...that was blooming quietly in abundance...
世界を変える力が
...whispers that the power to change the world...
その手にあると囁く
...is in your hands.
終わらない夢を見よう
Let us dream an unending dream...
君と行く時間の中で
...in the time we go with you.
想いだけが生きる全て
My feelings alone are all that I live for,
命を作るのは
and what creates life...
願い
...is a wish.
彼らを殺すためだけに復活させたの？
They brought them back to kill them off?
主人公を殺したのよ... 別に... 大所帯のキャストじゃないのに。文字通り2人しかキャラがいないのよ。
They killed a main character... like, not... it's not a big cast. It's literally just two characters.
何年も前に最終回を迎えた番組なのに、再結成エピソードを作って主人公を殺すなんて信じられない！本当に...
I can't believe that you would have a finale of a show years ago, and then you would do a reunion episode to kill the main character! It's so...
本当にバカバカしい。
It's so stupid.
なんてこと。まあ...
Oh my god. Well...
脚本家は何も分かってないわ！これじゃ稼げないじゃない！
These writers don't know what they're doing! That's not gonna make any money!
このアイデアはボツにすべきね。最悪のアイデアだわ。もう私のカノン（公式設定）じゃない。
We should trash this idea. This is a terrible idea. You know what? Not my canon.
私の公式設定じゃないわ。
Not my canon.
これは私の番組じゃない。
This is not my show.
そうよ。ただの金儲けだわ。大嫌い。
No, no. It's just a cash grab. I hate it.
分かった、分かった... 他にどんなものが金儲けか知ってる？
Okay, okay... You know what else is a cash grab?
なに？なに？
What? What?
オートフィスターのグッズよ！
The Autofister merchandise!
誰かこれについて説明してくれる人がいればいいのに。
If only we had someone here that could tell us about it.
これ... マイク入ってる？よし、オッケー。
Is this... is this thing on? Okay, great.
みなさん、こんにちは！森カリオペです...
Mina-san, hey everyone! It's me, Mori Calliope...
ホロライブEnglish -Myth-から、今日はこちらに来ています...
...from Hololive English Myth, coming here to you today...
このグッズを買っていただくためにお願いに参りました...
...to ask you to please purchase this merchandise...
オートフィスター・ネットのグッズセットです。
...the Autofister Net Merch Set.
グレムともキーホルダーや...
Ever wanted a Gremtomo keychain...
ジミミやセミミはいかがですか？
...or a Gimimi or Cemimi?
それとも、オートフィスターが描かれたアクリルスタンドがいいですか？
Or better yet, an acrylic stand with Autofister on it?
（熱狂の歓声）
Open parenthesis, noise of enthusiasm, close parenthesis.
おお... すごい！
Oh... oh wow!
格安価格の99.99ドル、［価格はピー音で消されます］
For the low low price 99.99, open bracket, price will be beeped, [beep], close bracket.
ごめんなさい... もう一回やらせて。これはあなたのものに！あなたのものになります！
Sorry, sorry, sorry... let me do it again. This can be yours! This can be yours!
そして今すぐ購入すれば、！！、この超素晴らしい言葉を大声で言います！
And if you purchase now, double exclamation point, I will say this one super awesome word out loud!
［意味深な沈黙］
Open bracket, pregnant silence, close bracket.
リーグ・オブ・レジェンド。これって... 2つの言葉だよね。
League of Legends. That's... that's two words.
待って、何が書いてあるか分かった。3つの言葉だわ。そんなの言わない。事前に台本チェックしたの？
Wait, okay, I see what's on there. That's three words. I'm not saying that. Did you check the script beforehand?
ああ、これは悪いアイデアだった、本当に最悪のアイデアだわ、なんで同意しちゃったんだろう、うう！
Ooh, this was a bad idea, this is a freaking bad idea, I don't know why I agreed to this, ooh!
...リーグ・オブ・レジェンド。ありがとうございました、そしてグッズを買ってください。
...League of Legends. Thank you, and buy the merchandise.
わあ、ありがとうカリ！
Oh wow, thanks Calli!
私たちのことが大好きなのね。グッズも気に入ってくれたわ。
She loves us. She loves our merch.
イェーイ！
Yeah!
Grow up, nah mean?
Track, Giga!
あぁー！
Ahhh!
子供騙しのマセマティカ
I'm over all this stupid mathematica
威張ってんだって そんなのって プライドなくない？
I don't care about a thing now, no pride left to hide
ご立派 警鐘 気取りで
Putting on a show but I'm over it now
高みの見物ばかりじゃつまんねぇ
Riding upon a horse up high, I wanna get down
ほらもっと 間違って上等
Again they don't see, that I'm really not king
退屈に手をかけて保存して
And every day repeating all the same
こんなところじゃ終われない
Mama, I don't know what to do, I couldn't stop it tonight
ぬるくて 気が触れそう
And maybe I'm going crazy
ごっこ遊びも芝居もさようなら
In a fantasy of make believe, I'm living my life, say goodbye
ずっとこのままだなんてさ... 嫌なんだよ
I don't want to stay like this forever... I hate it!
ダッダッダ あたし大人になる
Da da da, I'm growing up and out into the world
酸いも甘いも噛み分けて今
Tasting all of the sweet, maybe even sour things
パッパッパ 変わる時代
Pa pa pa, I'm changing up, believe
悪いことばかりじゃないでしょう
In every word that I say, because it's coming from me
過去も、罪も、罰も、すべて
All the past, all the sin, all the pain I was in
素手で、愛で 生き抜いてやり返すわ
Make it through with my hands, with love, surviving all that I can
yeah, 挑発 あたしたちはno doubt
Yeah, we out, making you crazy no doubt
緑のアイツにばっか構ってんね
Don't be talking about that green one with no flow again
さぁburn up いつになったら貰える合格
Yeah, so burn up as I pass in the rearview, so what?
赤ペンいれてよ どこがダメなんですか
Need a pen? Any red? Bet I get a hundred and ten like I said
酒女金ドラッグ やっちゃってコンプラ
Girls, liquor, money, and drugs, you know they're gonna say yes
剥がれ落ちたメイク
The mask comes off
すっぴんのアニマル
and the beast comes out, barefaced animal
醜くてもやっちゃうのよ
I do it wild even if it's ugly
おすわりとかできない
I can't do "sit"
だって待ってもできない
I can't even do "stay"
喉鳴らして いっちゃうまで
Purr until I go
がぶっとしよっか
You want me to bite you?
高まるビート
Accelerating beat
良いも悪いも全然しよ
Let's do both the good and bad
ハマってみよっか
Let's get lost in each other,
突破するゲート
plunge into the gate
愛に期待は禁物だよ
Expectations in love are forbidden
Let's go!
がたがたくだらない
Rattling, so pointless
言葉ばかりが譲れない
Nothing but words, I won't back down
分かるかあたしの美学
Do you understand my aesthetic?
このバイブス正直な
These honest vibes
拳一つが
A single fist
絆なんです
is our bond
切り札
The trump card
うつくなんです
is beauty
ガナるラッタトゥ
Snarling rat-a-too
一撃のKO
A single blow KO
サイレンバー
Siren bar
Ow!
Are you guys ready? Every single person...
...at home, put your hands up!
Come on!
Hey!
こんなもんじゃない
It's not just this
だんだんぼくらおとなになる
Gradually, we become adults
酸いも甘いもかみわけていま
Having experienced both the sour and sweet now
散々交わる未来を
Our paths cross so many times in the future
脅すこともないのよ
There's nothing to threaten us
分かるでしょう
You understand, right?
嫌い
Hate
待ってくれない
Won't wait
つれない態度で
With a cold attitude
生き抜いて頂戴
Please survive
Ahhhhh!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
それでは皆様 お先にバイキャッ
Well then everyone, bye-bye for now!
動画が、終わりました！
The video has finished!
Are you thinking...
...what I'm thinking?
I think I am!
Oh my god, we have to bring this. Write this down!
Write this down right now! We're going to take it to the suits!
Yes!
Oh my god, they're gonna love this.
They're gonna love it.
They're gonna love us. They love us. They love us.
This is bad.
This... is... bad...
I'm going to give up on my dreams.
N-Never give up on your dreams!
Really?
Yeah, I feel like... you had half a good idea.
And you had half a good idea too.
And together...
That's a... we'll...
...whole good idea.
That's a whole good idea. We'll get the funding one day.
Well, thank you very much everyone that helped us work on all these shows together.
Thank you to all our beautiful, wonderful guests!
And thank you to you, grems and otomos!
At home, watching us today...
...during our TV show!
Please sign our petition,
Look at the credits!
And look at the credits! And don't forget, there is something else coming up in just a few minutes!
Very special!
Right after this, so don't change the channel!
Don't change the channel just yet! Put down that remote. Put it down.
Put down that remote!
Yes, gun to your head, put it down right now!
Put down the remote right now! There's something really, really cool coming up right after this!
Yay!
The...
...Autofister Network!!!